Contact

+37494090589 (Mobile) vaheyavrumyan@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yavrumian (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Kubernetes

Terraform

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Languages

Armenian (Native or Bilingual)
Russian (Elementary)
English (Professional Working)

Vahe Yavrumian

DevOps engineer

Yerevan, Armenia

Summary

With over 5 years of experience in Information Technologies, I am a hardworking individual who strives to achieve the best in all areas. Friendly, self-organized, and genuinely in love with my industry. Now that I have acquired more skills, I intend on working within a company where I can develop and utilize my skill set while achieving my personal goals of becoming a competent, respected, and successful professional. Fast learner, self-motivated, applying methods and technical updates in my day-to-day work with a high degree of attention and commitment to work.

Experience

Freelance
DevOps Engineer
July 2022 - Present (4 months)
Yerevan, Armenia

Due-X LLC Node.js developer February 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Education

NPUA high school High School Diploma, Engineering · (2017 - 2020)